<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://mechagic.party/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All my writing</title>
    <link>https://mechagic.party/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://mechagic.party/2feed/feeds.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>My writing, wow so cool</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>That stupid thing called &quot;overthinking&quot;</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/That_stupid_thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I feel like day by day I get more violent but only to a certain extent, I&#39;m sure if I write about violence it will let itself out that way. I just want to make it all end faster, but not in a &amp;quot;stay away from sharp objects&amp;quot; more so a &amp;quot;stay in bed more&amp;quot; way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m pretty sure I need a therapist, I doubt I&#39;m getting one anytime soon though. My mom says I can &amp;quot;tell her everything&amp;quot; but I&#39;ve tried telling her things in the past, and guess what: I cannot in fact tell her everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She&#39;s an oxymoron in that regard, claiming to listen but not. It&#39;s annoying actually, almost as annoying as people saying &amp;quot;I don&#39;t know&amp;quot; on a discord server when you ask a question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Worse is, she also doesn&#39;t take in any of it and starts saying that what I think is wrong, not even letting me explain myself, she shouts and it&#39;s bad and I don&#39;t like it very much methinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if the “therapy” option isn’t available, and so is the “mom” option, the third option is ranting to what is either the void, a ridiculous amount of internet strangers, or something in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Worst case scenario is a youtuber finding this website and saying I’m cringe, which would have me getting cyber bullied on the internet and this would then have me cause a horrific incident to myself or someone else. This would end with a bunch of people on Tumblr or Tiktok or whatever saying “oh look how we failed this young person guys, lets all get sad about it”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m looking too far into the future with that last scenario, making too many assumptions. Someone I know online once told me that I might have anxiety, I don’t think I do. I’m pretty sure I don’t have that knocking around my braincase. I should stop with that and end this blog post here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 24:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/That_stupid_thing/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am so tired</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/I_am_so_tired/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am tired of everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m tired that a country I don&#39;t live in can influence the one I do live in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m tired that my father that lives in America is a flawed stupid old man that voted for an even more flawed stupid old man 3 times in a row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will be fine, it will probably be a fluke as well, the votes aren&#39;t done being counted yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just want this to end soon, I am so tired of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I eat, sleep, shit, piss, go to school, learn stuff I don&#39;t care about and it could all end at any moment, and it&#39;s fine I&#39;m fine with this. I&#39;ll just keep going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You too, by the way, you should also keep going forward, even if it gets annoying at some point.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;bx2&quot;&gt;
Have a list of mental health stuff in this trying time, all of them should be, or at least link to, something that&#39;s available worldwide
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suicide hotlines - &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domestic Violence hotlines, as well as resources - &lt;a href=&quot;https://safeandtogetherinstitute.com/international-domestic-violence-resources/&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sexual, as well as domestic, abuse agencies - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotpeachpages.net/a/countries.html&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trans resources - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotpeachpages.net/a/countries.html&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 24:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/I_am_so_tired/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hanahaki Ideas</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/Hanahaki_Ideas/</link>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanahaki that isn&#39;t based on love itself but can come from other emotions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of it originating from lack of interest in the other person, the hanahaki forces someone to actually confess, reciprocation of feelings isn&#39;t required to cure someone, hanahaki would be caused by the repression of emotions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essentially, hanahaki is just your body telling you: actually tell them how you feel, you idiot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanahaki can come from many emotions: anger, love, hate etc... The flowers depend on the feelings, the amount varies depending on how intense the emotions are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asters for love, aconites for anger, among other things. Five flowers being coughed up are usually cured by vague posting online about the other person, ten flowers can be cured via indirect confession, but more than fifteen flowers have to be cured by directly confessing to the other. More flowers = more extreme the confession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flowers that represent worry are more common during times of plague, while love flowers would be more common during times of peace. Friendship flowers are the most common types of flowers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hanahaki can be dangerous but easily manageable so long as someone can afford the right medicine to avoid flare-ups, in more extreme cases the victim is either encouraged to go get surgery, which has the side effect of numbing any emotions for the other person, or to just confess&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a person dies, it&#39;s traditional for people to cough up grieving flowers and collect them to be used as decoration for the person&#39;s grave.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 24:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/Hanahaki_Ideas/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>