<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://mechagic.party/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All my writing</title>
    <link>https://mechagic.party/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://mechagic.party/2feed/feeds.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>My writing, wow so cool</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>NeoPronoun Stuffs</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/Neopronoun_Stuffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m going to ramble about something very niche here
I&#39;ve noticed that in some things, they claim that &amp;quot;gender&amp;quot; doesn&#39;t exist but then they turn around and give their characters the same cookie-cutter pronouns we have in our own universe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which is confusing, because doesn&#39;t gender NOT exist here or something?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do get the reasoning though, making up new pronouns is hard but I have a few ideas I came up with&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pronouns based on the characters physical appearance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eg: A character with green eyes would go by &amp;quot;green/greenself&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pronouns that are variations of the characters name&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eg: Warren goes by war/warself or ren/renself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pronouns based on status/profession&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eg: a librarian that goes by book/bookshelf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pronouns based on the characters personality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eg: A stealthy character that goes by sly/slyself&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got more actually, what if the pronouns are given to the characters by their parents? Like how names are given to us by our parents&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay that&#39;s it, bbye&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/Neopronoun_Stuffs/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bees In Your House</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/Bees_in_your_house/</link>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;box2&quot;&gt;Note: These are all messages I sent in the nekoweb discord server that I decided to post here :}, it&#39;s essentially me shitting on people that punish mobile users for visiting their website for no reason lol&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website that sends bees to your house the moment you visit it on anything thats not a nintendo ds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website that sends the &amp;quot;you are an idiot&amp;quot; virus to all your devices if you visit it on something that&#39;s not the wii&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The WiiU doesn&#39;t count&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website that leaks your address online if you access it with a smart fridge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website that gives you a child if you access it on the WiiU&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Wii counts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where do the children come from, where do the children go? Toddler joe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website that turns your loved ones to gold if your name starts with the letter M&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonus that&#39;s not in the nekoweb discord: Making your website redirect to a rickroll if someone visits on mobile&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/Bees_in_your_house/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining the Name of This Page</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/Explaining_the_name/</link>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;
    h3{
        margin-left: 3rem!important;
    }
    span.sml{
        margin-left: 0rem!important;
        margin-right: 0rem!important;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, that&#39;s right buddy. I am finally making my first journal post in 2025 on... March the 2nd... Uh oh. Gotta come up with something fast! Luckily I have been thinking of this post for a while except not really because it has been on the backburner ever since I changed the name of this page from a &amp;quot;blog&amp;quot; to a &amp;quot;journal&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways I should stop meandering, as you have probably read from the description of the pervious page, it should probably be the just and all that there is to say. Except! It is not (plot twist amiright?). I&#39;ll just list out the reasons as to why it is the way it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Feels less professional&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay so like Blog feels too business-y to me, probably because my mom used to have one and used it solely for the purpose of getting money via advertisements. As you can see through out this whole website, this is just for funsies and also there are no ads &lt;span class=&quot;sml&quot;&gt;unless somewhere down the future I add stuff like johnvertising, but that doesn&#39;t really count&lt;/span&gt;. Woah what was that weird whisper? Okay onto the next reason!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. It&#39;s longer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Journal is a longer word than blog and that is important because the other link names on the &lt;code&gt;Navigation&lt;/code&gt; section of my website feel like they fit in with each other &lt;span class=&quot;sml&quot;&gt;don&#39;t talk about the extras page, I&#39;m planning to change it to miscellaeny in the future anyways&lt;/span&gt; Before you say &amp;quot;It still feels shorter compared to the rest&amp;quot;, yes I &lt;strong&gt;know&lt;/strong&gt; but also this is my own website and I can do what I want with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. I like it&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s a word thats got pizzazz y&#39;know? And in the words of our lord and saviour Greg Heffley &amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;OK, let me get something straight: This is a JOURNAL, not a diary.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;quot; The word diary kinda sucks ass and I don&#39;t like it (I am exteremely biased)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that is the end of this Journal Post, idk how to send these off, g&#39;bye and have a nice day or whatever&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/Explaining_the_name/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am so tired</title>
      <link>https://mechagic.party/journal/I_am_so_tired/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am tired of everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m tired that a country I don&#39;t live in can influence the one I do live in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m tired that my father that lives in America is a flawed stupid old man that voted for an even more flawed stupid old man 3 times in a row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will be fine, it will probably be a fluke as well, the votes aren&#39;t done being counted yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just want this to end soon, I am so tired of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I eat, sleep, shit, piss, go to school, learn stuff I don&#39;t care about and it could all end at any moment, and it&#39;s fine I&#39;m fine with this. I&#39;ll just keep going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You too, by the way, you should also keep going forward, even if it gets annoying at some point.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;bx2&quot;&gt;
Have a list of mental health stuff in this trying time, all of them should be, or at least link to, something that&#39;s available worldwide
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suicide hotlines - &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domestic Violence hotlines, as well as resources - &lt;a href=&quot;https://safeandtogetherinstitute.com/international-domestic-violence-resources/&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sexual, as well as domestic, abuse agencies - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotpeachpages.net/a/countries.html&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trans resources - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotpeachpages.net/a/countries.html&quot;&gt;link &lt;i class=&quot;ph ph-link&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>MECHAGIC</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://mechagic.party/journal/I_am_so_tired/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>